# Teen Kar Seng

Email: teenkar@gmail.com

Based in: Singapore

Phone: (+65) 9722 7928

#### **Cover Letter**

I am a Junior year student at Berklee College of Music pursuing a Bachelor of Arts in Songwriting and Music Production.

I am highly proficient with ProTools and experienced in audio editing, mixing and sound design. I have worked on several student projects throughout my coursework. In particular, I found game audio to be one of my greatest strengths and developed passion for it. In addition, I can write and produce music for a variety of genres and use cases.

My other competencies include video editing, graphic design and photography, having graduated with a diploma in Communications & Media Management from Temasek Polytechnic.

I have been playing Blizzard games since I was very young with Warcraft 3. I also played Diablo 3, Starcraft 2, Hearthstone and HOTS early in their releases. Similarly, I have played Overwatch since it was released and it had quickly become my favorite Blizzard franchise. It would be my greatest pleasure to have the opportunity to work and learn at Blizzard on new Overwatch content. Having also spent much time playing other games in the FPS genre, namely CSGO, Valorant and Apex Legends, I believe my understanding of the technical demands in the genre as a consumer would be useful fitting in this role.

Thank you for considering my application!

# Portfolio Website

#### https://tksaudio.com

#### Education

Bachelor of Arts, Songwriting and Producing Music, Berklee College of Music, Boston, Massachusetts.

April 2020 - Present

• Current CGPA: 3.98

Diploma, Communications and Media Management, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore.

April 2016 - May 2019

• Graduated CGPA: 3.48

## Skills

Avid ProTools

Audiokinetic Wwise

FMOD Studios

Unity Engine (Basic)

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe Photoshop

Sound Design

Music Production

Music Writing

HTML/CSS & JavaScript

Video Production

Photography

### Experience

#### Freelance Audio Editor

**Adobe After Effects** 

May 2021

• Performed recording, editing and mixing of voice-overs for a college level prototype product design video.

Microsoft Office

# Marketing Intern MediaCorp Pte Ltd, Singapore

April 2018 - September 2018

- Filmed and edited videos for social media marketing.
- Graphic Design to create posters and banners for use on digital website and printed for physical use.
- Collaborated with team members to help expand marketing channels.
- Monitored and analyzed impressions, reach and engagements on social media marketing campaigns.
- Handled social media accounts for company.

#### Military

# National Service, Republic of Singapore Air Force (RSAF)

May 2019 - May 2021

• 2-year mandatory enlistment to the Singapore National Service with the RSAF.

# Language

- English (Spoken, Written) First Language
- Mandarin Chinese (Spoken, Written) Proficient

# Achievements

- 3rd Place at POL-ITE Water Polo competition, 2017 & 2018
- The Dream Composition Songwriting Competition Finalist, 2018

MediaCorp Major Project Prize for Best Major Project Group, 2019

• 4th Place at National B Division Floorball competition, 2015